hello and welcome back to another
episode of hermitcraft these pigmen are
really getting out of hand i really
should close this up in some way but i
also
don't want to ruin the look of my portal
now i've obviously been on the server
working on a few projects here which
we're going to come back to later but
this has appeared and it says green's
hermit gift which is a bit suspicious
already there's a book and quill in here
and i haven't read this i've no idea
what it says yet but
i actually need to come back to this
because i actually really want to finish
what i'm doing over here before i go and
pursue something else because i've been
putting this off for a long time now
i've talked about the layers being
slightly useless
and
listen i really want to make a farm and
i don't really care if everyone already
has a farm and i know i've already got a
small farm there but i want to do
something a little bit better here so
what i'm gonna do is make a few tubes
that go up like this
or just just two and one of them will
have some reeds in them and the other
will have like pumpkins melons
and some cactus thrown in there as well
maybe just so that i'm actually
producing something because at the
moment i am just a full-on consumer of
everything and i've prepared quite a lot
of this stuff so i'm gonna quickly wrap
up one of these tubes in a little time
lapse and then we can crack on with all
the other things that we need to do
today don't panic this timelapse is only
going to take 30 seconds there's not
even any time to answer questions from a
q a i decided to give it my own go at
designing this i didn't look at any read
files which was probably a mistake i
just copied the one that i had in my
corner and scaled it up and guess who
decided not to press f1 when they were
time-lapsing yeah that's right me so you
can see the chat going nuts and you
don't even need to pause it and check
what it was we were just charging a
scout 3000 diamonds for a bunch of paper
and then you can see i actually died
right about here you can see all my
items and then i went and retrieved them
that's actually where i'm gonna leave it
i'm not even gonna start this one here
because i know that the design is not
efficient i'm a little bit worried about
the lag so i want to just leave it as it
is for now give it a test i can see that
everything's already growing now this is
the kind of design that is very
granesque so as you can see it detected
that but it's not done anything that's
because on the other side as soon as
that bit goes up both parts will then
get pushed it's so put together with
duct tape and bubble gum it's it's so
weird but it works the whole thing does
work and i'm proud because it's my
design i didn't copy anyone
ah but that means it is rubbish as well
and on top of that i'm super curious
what's going on in here also last
episode you may remember that i started
selling stuff for some emeralds now that
was because i wanted to make some backup
gear in case i lost it i have kitted
myself out with a couple of chests worth
of stuff it's it's just a backup thing
in case anything happens to uh my armor
because it takes hours and hours to sort
that out anyway let's crack on with this
green's hermit gift all right brienne
there is a treasure for you on a pirate
ship see it as a welcome gift for being
the newest hermit head to cleo's pirate
ship right next to it there'll be a
ghost ship follow the signs that's it
that's it just go to cleo's ship okay so
head to cleo's pirate ship right next to
it there's another one and then follow
the signs
oh my goodness there is
oh i see what they mean by ghost ship
it's made out of glass as well oh i like
the effect there what's going on here
then
where are the signs ah sign here
spin the key
it doesn't do anything
it's done nothing
oh
oh oh my goodness oh that's scared
the life out of me oh my god
so there's nothing really here except
spin the key which
i have done there's nothing
nothing happening
is there anything else for me to find
here
there's absolutely nothing except find
the key
oh no no what okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay i'm getting potions thrown at
me everywhere okay what do they say
gonna impulse and do i have to kill
these guys i think i gotta kill them to
stop this
how do i stop this how do i stop this
okay hold still hold still
i totally released
uh
i totally wasn't supposed to kill them
are you kidding me
for real
it was it was a present for being the
new hermit
oh that's so genius
hold on i need to go and get my stuff
back
i'll just use this stuff to go and grab
it i have a feeling
that i have just been
properly bamboozled
i am so confused
why
why has this happened to me
i mean don't get me wrong it's
absolutely genius
oh look at that flag as well the masters
are seriously cool oh this really does
look like a ghost ship and it feels like
it too
so
spinning the key did nothing but as soon
as i removed it yep there's all my stuff
now if i'm super smart about this
get out of here
he's wearing all my stuff i think it's
out it's out of potions by the looks of
things
nope not quite so ren and doc did this
to me
unbelievable
[Laughter]
okay
that i mean that was good i think one of
do each of these do something different
that's what i want to know
i figured that there was uh basically a
pressure plate on here that when i came
down and if i killed one of them it
released the others i thought i could
get away with this
[Laughter]
okay i gotta admit i was more scared
by the puffer fish
there we go oh no
oh i almost made it to be honest with
you i don't know what i expected
but it wasn't
wren captain ren and doc in the form of
zombies killing me but this is so
oh my okay i failed that
i'm just i'm just i'm oh for goodness
sake
ah back again where's all my other stuff
gone
wait it's there oh i completely missed
this sign
it said green this way for your treasure
so i missed that i i just skipped right
to the last sign green this is the way
to your treasure
try and get it back from our crusty
krusty out crusty crew
and then spin the key all i saw was spin
the key so that was super confusing
look at the effort that these guys have
gone through
to get me
what did i ever do to them i don't think
oh wait yeah okay i totally i totally
pranked ren and that's probably why this
is happening but i i hope that he got
false just as much because the only
reason that i did the prank with false
was because she had that item like i i
was just doing my my duty so i i guess
that's why but i don't know why doc's
involved but can we just take a second
to appreciate the massive boat that they
made just to kill me
oh i see so all the redstone is like
down here i didn't even see that that is
so
so clever it's beautifully made and on
top of that cleo gets a free boat
right next to hers
i love the flag i love everything about
this this is so funny i mean fair play
guys um thank you for welcoming me to
the surfer but you know i can't let this
i can't let this go you know that right
you've started something and i'm gonna
finish it you can't just go and prank me
to no end just because i'm the new guy
so
i'm going to have to
i'm gonna have to do something
ren and doc so ren has the grand central
station and i already pranked that
doc i don't even know where doc's base
is but they both made the stock exchange
so maybe i can do something with that
in fact
in fact i have a really good idea which
i'm going to go and prep for now
my idea may or may not have something to
do with breaking in
to the stock exchange but i actually
know how to get in but i need someone
else's help to do it because of the way
that it works i think now what i plan on
doing to these guys is going to take a
little bit of preparation so i'm going
to have to spend a bit of time getting
some resources together so i'm gonna
have to do that a little bit later on
but for now what i actually wanted to do
last episode but i didn't get the chance
was to make a bunch of plants on my base
to give it a bit more life and greenery
so that's what we're going to try and do
now so maybe i should make a couple of
testers first so maybe just like a
flower bed because i want to make it
seem like this place isn't just like
super dead or and so futuristic that we
don't need plants anymore because that
would be ridiculous so it'd be great to
make this work and maybe if i use spruce
trap doors or something i can make this
work
let's give it a go this is just going to
be a little test example to see what
this might look like in context and
there's a neat little trick that i found
with pumpkins like put one here with a
pickle on top and it yeah it looks like
a little stem it's really cute add a few
flowers
but the main thing for this
is the leaves the leaves in the form
of plants
so i don't know about having any like
actual wood in here but if i build up
the
leaves enough and make it look messy
somehow can make it look like actual
bushes of some kind
okay it looks kind of weird on its own
but i think with that all the way around
that actually doesn't look too bad maybe
i should change the spruce to birch or
something
slightly more light-colored
to match the white or maybe even i get
just some more white concrete and create
a barrier using that let's let's
experiment further i want to see how
this goes so lots of grass
all right let's take a step back and see
what that looks like and
you know what that doesn't actually look
too bad it's just subtle enough that it
works maybe if i move all of that grass
down a block it would work or
because i don't know if this
needs another layer of white concrete
powder again or just white concrete i
don't i don't think that would look
right with it there so maybe i need to
move that down just one block and then i
can add some more detail in there but
i'd like to get your guy's opinion first
before i actually commit to putting this
on every single layer because that's a
lot of work there so what i'm thinking
is right now
we need to get some more like long grass
and double long grass i think that's
basically what it's called and i want to
move all of this down all of this stuff
goes down one layer so it's actually
inside here so i may not even need a
block to put here as it's all down
inside the top of this and then that
gives it like a really nice layer of
green and that introduces a new color to
this palette now you don't take it
exactly as it is i won't maybe make the
the leaves go that high because it looks
really small
however i think with context every
single layer with a bit of green or
splash of color a bit of life might look
good
i'll leave i'll leave a poll up there
for you guys to vote on but for now i
think i'm gonna remove this since i'm
gonna have to move it down a layer
anyway
so let me know what you guys think now
i've been thinking about how i'm going
to get back ren and doc
for what they did to me
which is really funny and i think i've
got something that's equally as funny
maybe not quite as big when it comes to
the building side of things
but i think it's really funny
nonetheless but i'm gonna need some help
okay so i've prepared everything i've
got my shulker box full of goodies and i
know exactly what i want to do with it
but because i need two people to get in
there i've asked the help of tango who
is online at the moment now i don't
really want to be typing in the chat
what i'm going to be doing so i'm going
to message tango to let him know that
i'm ready and then i'm going to meet up
with him i have a way to make sure that
i am not blamed for this and it's going
to be absolutely brilliant good to go
excellent now tango has absolutely no
idea what i'm going to do i've just told
him that i need help getting into the
stock exchange and he's here to help me
i actually forgot that i'm gonna need
some levels for this because i've got a
plan i've got a plan so i've got myself
some levels i've got myself some more
materials and tango is now waiting for
me to meet up with him
oh my goodness i forgot about this is no
one gonna clean up that poop for real so
this is tango's base i don't think we've
actually ever been here apart from when
i was annoying him on his stream he's
built like this giant under whoa
hello tango oh
what's up good sir how are you i am very
fine i've only ever been here when
you're streaming to annoy you uh-huh
looks like it's coming along
it's getting there it's getting there so
much much to be done but yeah i'm having
fun so what's the the lone house over
there is that is that your base
no no no this is my this is my storage
room i just built this um finally you
know the season's already like six
months over uh no that house over there
is like just a sample of the village i'm
gonna make down here it looks so cool
dude anyway that's not why i'm here
though why um why i'm here and why i ask
for your help is i told you that i want
to break in to the stock exchange
but i didn't tell you why because i was
scared that you would say no but it's
too late now you've said yes
of course i mean first of all it's a
mischief so sign me up
so
there's been like a cascade of events
that have led to this i've been kind of
aware it all started with the with the
false poop incident right yeah so that
happened then false got me and her to
prank wren
but it turns out it wasn't wren
so okay
they've pranked me in return they gave
me this book and it's said to go to
cleo's base where they've built like
this weird ghost ship and it killed me
oh man and
yeah i was i was killed by two zombies
in a hole with ren and doc's face on it
just to take those
does dirty yeah yeah yeah okay okay so i
i don't feel too good about that so what
i'm what i'm planning to do is go to the
stock exchange which they spent like
weeks right they tell them where it
where it hurts and
i think it's better that i explain when
we get there but i need your help to get
in so
i mean i yeah i'm i'm totally on board i
just i don't know much about the stock
exchange so let's go
cool but first i'm going to send you an
outfit because this is borderline
criminal what we're doing so i want to
try and get away with it if i can
so i'm going to send you a disguise and
we should put those on because i think
it'll help
[Laughter]
do your best do your best false
impression hello grier
hello
i'm full symmetry
[Laughter]
right well i'm i'm totally not tangled i
i'm green obviously but i under here i'm
actually mumbo jumbo
so i think we can get away with this
okay
because
i'm gonna disguise myself as green so
that it looks like green is actually
doing it but it's clearly mumbo under
here and i i i think i could do a pretty
uh a pretty good mambo impression let me
let me hear your mumbo
hello everyone this is mumbo and welcome
back to another hermitcraft video
right
better than my fault give me that better
than my fault
anyway so i think this is foolproof
of course i mean no one can break
through this code exactly no one's gonna
figure out that i'm secretly mumbo and
you're not false symmetry right right
right
so how do we start the mischief what are
we doing well first we gotta go to the
stock exchange oh i forgot
no
dude this place is deadly
dude
no i'm already dead
oh my goodness i totally forgot that we
took all that
[Applause]
i jumped off like a sheep right after
you
oh my goodness
you must have seen that i wasn't wearing
it
it was like a split second after
well that that but this heist is off to
a fantastic start i mean yeah clearly
we're professional criminals here
all right shall we try again yeah now
with flight technology yay let's go
amazing
oh wait i'm going the wrong way
okay here we are stock exchange now
excellent i already know how to get in
because i was like sneaking around and i
was watching them so i already know
roughly how to get in there might be a
few details i'm missing
okay i haven't been in here in ages i
never actually bought any stock either
neither i i haven't been involved in
this at all but all i know is there's
like buttons here right is this the part
where you need me yeah exactly right so
there's two sides here you can see one
with ren and one with doc and you have
to push the button you're not going to
just like
extinguish me or something or not
if you're in you're in you're in that's
suddenly got a bad feeling about this
okay
all right so all you got to do is rotate
this seven times but we got to do it at
the same time i believe but you've got
to like let the light go off and on to
give it time to register all right you
ready one
two
three
four
five
six
seven
[Music]
that's like the best door in the world
that's amazing i am impressed with that
all right let's uh call the elevator
then
[Music]
i can't tell whether we just went up or
down
well this is this is where we need to be
oh i haven't actually
even told you what you were doing here
we're not here to steal stocks i'm not
interested in pieces of paper
we
we need to get in here because in here
is the good stuff i'm telling you good
stuff if you guys are stacks on stacks
of diamonds what is it
exactly it's stacks and stacks of
diamonds
they're in the right place yeah there's
a combination here but i don't actually
know the combination i saw ren do it but
i i don't remember but there can't be
that many combinations of this right oh
is this like a punching the floor kind
of combination yeah i think you gotta
right click it
[Music]
i hear things moving down there don't
worry last time that i just mashed it
and i got in
[Music]
come on
no ladies and gentlemen professional cat
burglar
there's only so many combinations right
look at this right okay so they wronged
me okay they they obviously yes they
killed me now i don't know if you've
ever been in here before
but i haven't if you press this
this is all of their good stuff look at
that diamonds in the hot tub there's
diamonds back here oh it's a treasure
bath right literally look at the things
bouncing
so what we're gonna do is we're gonna
replace these with green and tango heads
i love it i love it
now let me be clear before we go into
this i'm not stealing a single diamond
okay this is a personal game this is
simply revenge i want to make them panic
and we're actually just going to leave
these diamonds somewhere in the vicinity
they won't know where and i won't even
show it on camera but these diamonds
will not leave the room
green green
look at this did you see the bubbles in
the window i know how cool is this
they've spent so much on this so
professional oh my gosh
so we gotta get rid of all of these
diamonds in fact i kind of want to get
make sure that the green heads are
roughly exactly the same as they
are in the same in the same place okay
let me get the same place so just put
them on the ground right okay so now it
makes sense why i told you to bring some
of your own heads yeah yes i was
wondering i was wondering why but you
just got to trust you got to just trust
my madness basically and
there we go
oh that was that she didn't take that
long at all
nope nope that was good and then what we
need to do is we need to somehow get get
that stuff out of those uh out of the
hot tub like if we right click them can
i oh
did you just shift right click i just i
just was right-clicking
all right where are we gonna where are
we gonna hide the goods now okay uh well
i'm not gonna i'm not gonna show where
they are but what well i'm not gonna
show anyone where we hide the uh the
diamonds but of course we're clearly not
done here because they've got diamonds
going through here we've got a we've got
to add green and tango heads in here as
well the whole thing too the whole
shebang
oh i love it i love it all right let's
get busy so i actually brought some
anvils with me because i under actually
understand how this works they've got
all of these diamonds renamed to
something so that they don't all just
stack in the hoppers oh i see okay yeah
so we've got to do the same to the green
heads and if my if my redstone is
correct all we got to do is just replace
them have you got a couple of seconds
for me uh i do i do here you go
nice
so i've i've actually thought this
through i've planned this entire heist
out okay so all right if i do this
and then i i destroy these two the water
won't flow in but i can look at you i
can pick up the diamonds
uh and then just throw them back in the
water all of these diamonds are just
called like a diamond of uh
they're just cool i'm just kind of
spraying out here i don't have any more
tango heads though so we're gonna have
to do all green heads for this i think
okay i've got i've got plenty of green
heads you could uh you could suck a
couple of these back up
yeah the
[Laughter]
all right let's do tango heads on this
side then
they have just named them rubbish like d
humans get some lots of blood
yeah
oh wait there's still there's like a
pile of diamonds here i know i know
we're out of storage oh man i didn't
quite plan for this many diamonds i know
i know i mean either
we can use them we can use their their
one there they've got a white shulker
box i'm not gonna show on camera where
it is but i've taken the shulker boxes
full of diamonds and i'm gonna hide them
in this room somewhere in a chest so
they never even leave the room and ren
and doc won't have a clue where they are
love it
i put on most of these i've put
something like revenge or it wasn't me
or it was false
i can't believe how well this worked
right we gotta get rid of
i feel like there might be a couple more
uh armor stands in there maybe that we
can probably see
but that's fine we got the point across
yeah how do we how do we close this sand
door now we
right click um
yeah we just i think
we did it
so if they're not careful they will
they'll see that in there right they'll
if they're if they're not paying
attention true true true but that's okay
it's not second nature to them they'll
just walk right past it exactly right
okay i think we're like so in theory
this is what's going to happen then
we're going to wipe off all our
fingerprints
the next time
that doc
and ren come in here
they're gonna they're gonna come for a
jacuzzi with their latest client they're
going to right click this and this is
what they're going to see
[Laughter]
the client may change their mind i'll
just say that
[Laughter]
and the best thing is we don't need to
leave a sign nothing
no absolutely not it's just
and here's one deal right here's also
the beautiful thing if we take off if we
take off our outfits we should get a
screenshot as like an alibi
so we've got evidence that is
all right i'm gonna take a screenshot
got one of us there's no way they'll
figure out that this is us
no no we are
fool-proof
we've got we've got evidence that we
were never even here this was it it was
mumbo and false
all right let's close this up
oh this is a beautiful my friend
job well done they're gonna genuinely
think that we stole the diamonds when
they didn't go anywhere
right in fact we just gave them a bunch
of valuable heads
we did
if i ever start the uh the tango head
game
they gotta jump we gotta we gotta like
take a second to appreciate how much
excellent redstone went into this i
gotta say i assume it's dark and he goes
i mean this is mental
oh so good speaking of which actually
there's actually one more thing we need
to do
what's that what's that here hold on
take one of these i i told you i planned
this whole heist you can't do a heist
without planning it oh of course we got
it planning we got to go up here
oh
isn't that like the executive suite up
there yeah did you just break the
painting
i might have
i might
yeah yeah yeah that was that's it that
was it that was it
all right that's close we almost had our
cover blown there all right so they look
at this yeah exactly right but there's a
gold block there
i think
what would this look like
[Laughter]
anywhere there's an armor stand just
just pollute it with green heads i think
i got most of them
right
it's a bonsai green tree there's still
more i think okay i think i got all of
them this time brilliant that's
beautiful that is amazing
i think our work here is done
nothing more could be done this is
amazing and remember everyone watching
if anyone asks it was mumbo and false of
course we have evidence it was it was
mumbo
clearly dressed as green trying to frame
me right right right and he even used a
voice changer to sound just like me
unbelievable he's so clever that mumbo
jumbo
there you go all right thank you so much
dude for the hell oh my pleasure my
pleasure wouldn't have been able to get
in there otherwise
fantastic the heist is complete all
right now we gotta we gotta take our we
gotta take our disguises off and get
back to our normal hermitcraft doings
daily lives i'll see you later see you
later dude what is mumbo talking about
that was an insane thing that we just
did but mumbo said hey gree have you got
any levels i fell out my jet and needed
my elytra repaired and i said where are
you at my base and you can see my what
is he on about i need to catch up with
it
oh goodness
mumbo's up to no good again
i've just robbed a bank mumbo
i've got a spare lighter for him because
i actually don't have that many levels
he said he's at his base
uh
so i'm here
now what on earth is he on about
okay let's go
uh what on earth is he on about he's
made a jet
in hermitcraft but wait is that one of
those flying
wait
has he lost it that he went the wrong
way
oh my goodness this man doesn't know how
to fly
i can see the bottom of his feet
he's got like he's got like
he's not wearing any socks
what the heck it's over iskall's base at
the moment i'm i'm sorry mumbo i'm just
a little busy looking at your weird feet
why aren't you wearing shoes
he's like worn out the bottom of the
bottom of his feet oh oh oh i see it
oh that's why i started lagging
what is this
well i guess this is my life now well
i'm taking a lot of damage from this
machine and it seems to serve absolutely
no purpose except for cruising oh oh
this is so weird
well i think i think that's actually a
really good place to end this episode
so
today
we made a reed farm which is super bad
it's super badly made we also got
pranked by being led into a ghost ship
which looked awesome and we got killed
by doc and ren so in retaliation
me and tango went and raided his vault
and hid his diamond somewhere in that
room
and now i'm riding on a slime jet with
mumbo
the heck is going on in this server
anyway
thank you very much for watching
everyone
good
bye